let questions = {
    easy: [
      {
        question: "What is a group of witches called?",
        answers: ["A horde", "A crew", "A coven", "A batch"],
        correctAnswer: "A coven"
      },
      {
        question: "Traditionally, a silver bullet is supposed to kill which creature?",
        answers: ["Vampire", "Werewolf", "Zombie", "Siren"],
        correctAnswer: "Werewolf"
      },
      {
        question: "From which region in the world do pumpkins originate?",
        answers: ["Greece", "China", "Australia", "Central America"],
        correctAnswer: "Central America"
      },
      {
        question: "Which country celebrates The Day of the Dead?",
        answers: ["Argentina", "Italy", "Japan", "Mexico"],
        correctAnswer: "Mexico"
      },
      {
        question: "Transylvania is a region in which European country?",
        answers: ["Romania", "Croatia", "Austria", "Slovakia"],
        correctAnswer: "Romania"
      },
      {
        question: "Which country is considered the birthplace of Halloween?",
        answers: ["England", "Ireland", "USA", "Germany"],
        correctAnswer: "Ireland"
      },
      {
        question: "Which science fiction horror series from Netflix is set in the fictional town of Hawkins?",
        answers: ["Wednesday", "Stranger Things", "The Walking Dead", "Vampire Diaries"],
        correctAnswer: "Stranger Things"
      },
      {
        question: "What is the name of the doll from The Conjuring?",
        answers: ["Jilly", "Hannah", "Tammy", "Annabelle"],
        correctAnswer: "Annabelle"
      },
      {
        question: "Which phobia means you have an intense fear of Halloween?",
        answers: ["Acrophobia", "Claustrophobia", "Glossophobia", "Samhainophobia"],
        correctAnswer: "Samhainophobia"
      },
      {
        question: "Which rock singer infamously bit the head off of a live bat during a concert in 1982?",
        answers: ["James Hetfield", "Ozzy Osbourne", "Rob Halford", "Alice Cooper"],
        correctAnswer: "Ozzy Osbourne"
      },
    ],
    medium: [
      {
        question: "Which U.S. city hosts the world's largest Halloween parade?",
        answers: ["Chicago", "New York City", "Detroit", "San Francisco"],
        correctAnswer: "New York City",
      },
      {
        question: "On average, what percentage of Americans carve a pumpkin for Halloween?",
        answers: ["25%", "35%", "45%", "55%"],
        correctAnswer: "45%",
      },
      {
        question: "What was the original title of the Michael Jackson song “Thriller”?",
        answers: ["Moonlight", "Starlight", "Zombie", "Moonshine"],
        correctAnswer: "Starlight",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the first name of Dr. Frankenstein?",
        answers: ["David", "John", "Victor", "James"],
        correctAnswer: "Victor",
      },
      {
        question: "What does the German word 'Poltergeist' literally translate to?",
        answers: ["Silent Death", "Noisy Ghost", "Loud Creature", "Silent Killer"],
        correctAnswer: "Noisy Ghost",
      },
      {
        question: "What was the name of the British film company which dominated the horror film market in the 50s, 60s & 70s?",
        answers: ["Isleworth Studios", "Hammer Films", "Dickenson Road Studios", "3 Mills Studios"],
        correctAnswer: "Hammer Films",
      },
      {
        question: "In the movie 'E.T.', what did E.T. dress as for Halloween?",
        answers: ["A ghost", "A scarecrow", "A clown", "A pirate"],
        correctAnswer: "A ghost",
      },
      {
        question: "How many times in history has Halloween fallen on Friday 13th?",
        answers: ["11", "24", "7", "0"],
        correctAnswer: "0"
      },
      {
        question: "What is the surname of Sabrina the teenage witch?",
        answers: ["Miller" ,"Spellman", "Shepherd", "Thatcher"],
        correctAnswer: "Spellman"
      },
      {
        question: "",
      }
    ],

    hard: [
      {
        question: "What's another name for a lycanthrope?",
        answers: ["Werewolf", "Vampire", "Gnome", "Nymph"],
        correctAnswer: "Werewolf",
      },
      {
        question: "Besides horror, what other genre did 'Dracula' author Bram Stoker publish books under?",
        answers: ["Fantasy", "Children's fiction", "Classic fiction", "Romance"],
        correctAnswer: "Romance"
      },
      {
        question: "What's the name of the terrifying clown in Stephen King's It, which was remade starring Bill Skarsgard in the title role?",
        answers: ["Freddy", "Pennywise", "Blade", "Nyx"],
        correctAnswer: "Pennywise"
      },
      {
        question: "The classic story Funnybones tells the story of a big skeleton, a little skeleton and what other type of skeleton?",
        answers: ["A cat's skeleton", "A dogs's skeleton", "An elephant's skeleton", "A tiger's skeleton"],
        correctAnswer: "A dog's skeleton"
      },
      {
        question: "What supernatural power does Carrie possess in Stephen King's blood-soaked novel of the same title?",
        answers: ["Conjuration", "Telekinesis", "Levitation", "Invisibility"],
        correctAnswer: "Telekinesis"
      },
      {
        question: "How many witches appear in Shakespeare's Macbeth?",
        answers: ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
        correctAnswer: "3"
      },
      {
        question: "Name the singer and actress that plays Mavis in Hotel Transylvania",
        answers: ["Taylor Swift", "Madonna", "Selena Gomez", "Miley Cyrus"],
        correctAnswer: "Selena Gomez"
      },
      {
        question: "In Monsters Inc, what is the name of the little girl who is not afraid of monsters?",
        answers: ["Tru", "Boo", "Sara", "Mae"],
        correctAnswer: "Boo"
      },
      {
        question: "What is the name of Billy's very cute and beleaguered mogwai in Gremlins?",
        answers: ["Bogart", "Gizmo", "Stripe", "Earl"],
        correctAnswer: "Gizmo"
      },
    ],
  };